Guide to the Bill Dixon Papers MSS.481
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Bennington College, 1964-1995, 2005; 88.26 Linear Feet in 30 record cartons, 29 flat boxes, 16 manuscript boxes, 4 tall LP boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 flat-file folder.; 40.26 Gigabytes in 42 digital files.
  - Subseries II.A: Class and Lecture Recordings, 1967-1994; 56.5 Linear Feet in 27 record cartons, 25 flat boxes, 3 LP boxes, and 1 manuscript box
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 9, 1971; cuid37961 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2186)
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 10, 1971; cuid37962 (Box 98, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2187)
      Reel 481_2187 in Box 98 was identified as moldy in September, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 12, 1971; cuid37963 (Box 61, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2246)
    - Black Music Ensemble Auditions, November 17, 1971; cuid37964 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2086)
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 23, 1971; cuid37965 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2188)
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 30, 1971; cuid37966
      - Audio -- 1 of 2, cuid44125 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2189)
      - Audio -- 2 of 2, cuid44126 (Box 98, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2190)
        Reel 481_2190 in Box 98 was identified as moldy in September, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
    - Black Music Ensemble, December 6, 1971; cuid37967 (Box 63, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2328)
    - Cheaters, Graduate Assistants Teaching Session, December 7, 1971; cuid37968 (Box 53, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1288)
    - Black Music Ensemble, December 8, 1971; cuid37969 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2192)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1972; cuid37970 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_155)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1972; cuid37974 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2169)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1972; cuid37975 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2147)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1972; cuid37978 (Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1368)
    - Black Music Ensemble, circa 1972; cuid37871 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1413)
    - Black Music Ensemble: "Piece #2" Rehearsal, 1972; cuid37977 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1411)
    - Black Music Lecture (Jan 13th), circa 1972; cuid37868 (Box 4, 1 inch video reel 481_011)
    - Lecture / Demonstration Voice Tape, circa 1972; cuid37870 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1456)
    - "Cheater", January 5, 1972; cuid37979 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_112)
    - "Cheater", January 8, 1972; cuid37980 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_113)
    - Black Music Lecture, January 11, 1972; cuid37981 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2163)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 1, 1972; cuid37982 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_168)
    - Black Music Ensemble -- Discussion with Jeff Cuspri, February 1, 1972; cuid37983 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2164)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 2, 1972; cuid37984 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2087)
    - Black Music Ensemble -- Manteca Rhythm Exercise, February 4, 1972; cuid37985 (Box 98, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2092)
      Reel 481_2092 in Box 98 was identified as moldy in September, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 7, 1972; cuid37986 (Box 63, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2329)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 11, 1972; cuid37987 (Box 63, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2330)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 14, 1972; cuid37988
      - Audio -- 1 of 2, cuid44127 (Box 98, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2146)
        Reel 481_2146 in Box 98 was identified as moldy in September, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
      - Audio -- 2 of 2, cuid44128 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1412)
    - Black Music Ensemble [?], February 15, 1972; cuid37989 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2088)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 16, 1972; cuid37990 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_142)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 18, 1972; cuid37991 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_141)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 22, 1972; cuid37992 (Box 52, Quarter inch audio reel 481_443)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 23, 1972; cuid37993 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_144)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 29, 1972; cuid37994 (Box 64, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2056, 481_2057, Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1382)
    - Black Music Ensemble, March, 1972; cuid37995 (Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1369)
    - Black Music Ensemble, March 4, 1972; cuid37997 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_145)
    - Black Music Ensemble Rehearsal, March 4, 1972; cuid37996 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_143, 481_146)
    - Black Music Ensemble for the Afro American Society, March 10, 1972; cuid37999 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1419)
    - Black Music Ensemble Lecture and Demonstration, March 10, 1972; cuid37998 (Box 61, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2279, 481_2280)
    - Black Music Ensemble, March 14, 1972; cuid38000
      - Audio -- 1 of 2, cuid44129 (Box 63, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2331)
      - Audio -- 2 of 2, cuid44130 (Box 98, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2165)
        Reel 481_2165 in Box 98 was identified as moldy in September, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
    - Black Music Ensemble -- Some Recursions and Instructions, March 20, 1972; cuid38001 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1415, 481_1416)
    - Black Music Ensemble, March 22, 1972; cuid38002 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_120, Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1381)
    - Black Music Ensemble, March 27, 1972; cuid38003 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_148)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April, 1972; cuid38004 (Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1364)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 9, 1972; cuid38005 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_123)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 11, 1972; cuid38006 (Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1365)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 14, 1972; cuid38007 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_124)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 16, 1972; cuid38008 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_125, 481_127)
    - Black Music Ensemble -- "Piece #2" Performed in Mills Hall, Broadcast WHA Radio, April 16, 1972; cuid38009 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1409)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 17, 1972; cuid38010 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_122, 481_126, Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Black Music Ensemble and Orchestra Pieces, April 18, 1972; cuid38011 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_129, 481_130)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 21, 1972; cuid38012 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2167)
      Note says "Prep for one of the pieces that is on FORE."
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 24, 1972; cuid38013 (Box 50, Quarter inch audio reel 481_209)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 25, 1972; cuid38014 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_131, Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1366)
    - Black Music Ensemble, April 26, 1972; cuid38015 (Box 61, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2281)
    - Black Music Ensemble -- Rehearsal of Pat Lagg Piece, May 1, 1972; cuid38016 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_149)
    - Black Music Ensemble, May 2, 1972; cuid38018 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_150, 481_151)
    - Black Music Ensemble, May 8, 1972; cuid38020 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_154)
      Duration: 86 minutes; Preservation note: Discussion before the musical interlude is at a very low volume
    - Black Music Ensemble, May 9, 1972; cuid38021 (Box 61, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2282, Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1450, Box 55, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1367)
    - Ensemble III Lecture and Demonstration -- "Elements of Composition and Contemporary Improvisation for the Musician", Fall, 1972; cuid37973 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2220)
    - Black Music Ensemble, October 19, 1972; cuid38022 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2168)
    - Elements of Composition and Contemporary Improvisation for the Musician -- Presentation by Student Worker, Carriage Barn, November, 1972; cuid38023 (Box 63, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2341)
    - Black Music Ensemble Discussion with Jeff Cuspri, December 4, 1972; cuid38024 (Box 60, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2162)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1973; cuid38027 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2135)
    - Meeting Regarding Black Music, 1973; cuid38025 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_132)
    - Class Rehearsal, April 19, 1973; cuid38030 (Box 52, Quarter inch audio reel 481_433, 481_434)
    - Ensemble, May 3, 1973; cuid38031 (Box 53, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1307)
    - Bennington College, May 10, 1973; cuid38032 (Box 50, Quarter inch audio reel 481_204, 481_210)
    - Ensemble IV -- First Meeting, September 13, 1973; cuid38033 (Box 53, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1308)
    - Ensemble, September 20, 1973; cuid38034 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_169)
    - Black Music Ensemble Rehearsal and Class, September 23, 1973; cuid38035 (Box 64, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1026)
    - Black Music Ensemble, Bennington College, September 27, 1973; cuid38036 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1438)
    - Black Music Ensemble Lecture and Performance, October 5, 1973; cuid38037 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2141, 481_2142)
    - Black Music Ensemble, October 23, 1973; cuid38038 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2140)
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 7, 1973; cuid38039 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2139)
    - Ted Joans Reading, Tishman Hall, November 9, 1973; cuid38040 (Box Shared Fales 106, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1030)
    - Ted Joans Workshop, Carriage Barn, November 11, 1973; cuid38041 (Box Shared Fales 106, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1028)
    - Black Music Ensemble, November 15, 1973; cuid38042 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2138)
    - Black Music Ensemble, Bennington College, November 29, 1973; cuid38043 (Box 52, Quarter inch audio reel 481_435, Box 28, Audiocassette 481_767)
    - Black Music Ensemble, Bennington College, December 6, 1973; cuid38044 (Box 52, Quarter inch audio reel 481_430)
    - Ensemble, and Beginning of Dance Improv Class, December 6, 1973; cuid38045 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_896)
    - Black Music Ensemble, December 13, 1973; cuid38046 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2136, 481_2137)
    - Class on Black Music Aesthetics, circa 1973-1974; cuid38029 (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1891)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38050 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2210)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38051 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2211)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38053 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2128)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38054 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2129)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38056 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1429)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38057 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1430)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38058 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1431)
    - Black Music Ensemble, 1974; cuid38060 (Box 56, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1424)
    - Orchestra Piece, 1974; cuid38059 (Box 43, Audiocassette 481_2487)
    - Black Music Ensemble, February 24, 1974; cuid38061 (Box 59, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2127)
    - Black Music Ensemble, May 9, 1974; cuid38062 (Box 52, Quarter inch audio reel 481_444)
      Duration: 63 minutes; Preservation note: Beginning has very low volume.
    - Percussion Workshop, May 29, 1974; cuid38063 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_116)
    - Lecture on Contemporary Improvisation, July, 1974; cuid38064 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_967)
    - Ensemble IV Rehearsal, October 17, 1974; cuid38065 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1451)
    - Ensemble IV Rehearsal, November 1, 1974; cuid38066 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2216, Box 61, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2237)
    - Octobersong Lecture and Demonstration for Ensemble III, November 3, 1974; cuid38067 (Box 43, Audiocassette 481_2479)
    - Ensemble IV Rehearsal and Concert, November 7, 1974; cuid38068 (Box 41, Audiocassette 481_1990)
    - Percussion Ensemble, Arthur Brooks, November 8, 1974; cuid38069 (Box 51, Quarter inch audio reel 481_172)
    - Black Music Ensemble, Winter, 1974; cuid38052 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2212)
    - Black Music Ensemble, Winter, 1974; cuid38055 (Box 57, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1428)
    - Black Music Lecture, Telephone Calls Regarding college, 1975; cuid38075 (Box 32, Audiocassette 481_1170)
    - Jimmy Stewart Lecture, March 24, 1975; cuid38081 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_117)
    - Stan Strickland, Black Music Workshop, April 28, 1975; cuid38082 (Box 49, Quarter inch audio reel 481_135)
    - Piano Lessons with Bill Dixon, Jennings Hall, Fall, 1975; cuid38070 (Box 20, Audiocassette 481_094)
    - Rehearsal with Larry Neal and Ensemble III, Fall 1975; cuid38074 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_864)
      Duration: 77 minutes; Preservation note: Dixon's verbal descriptions are at a much lower volume than the music.
    - Open Discussion, December 7, 1975; cuid38084 (Box 62, Quarter inch audio reel 481_2207)
    - Work in Progress for Ensemble and Voices, December 7, 1975; cuid38083 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_842)
    - Class discussion on the climate at Bennington and commercialism in music, circa 1975; cuid38076 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1784)
      Format: EIAJ-1; Duration: 34 minutes.
    - Discussion on faculty meeting and tenure issues, circa 1975; cuid38080 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1796)
      Format: EIAJ-1; Duration: 33 minutes.
    - Barn Music Demonstration, circa 1975-1980; cuid38079 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1790)
    - Bill Dixon Inc. Institute of Black Music Studies Research and Performance -- Compilation Tape, circa 1975-1980; cuid38077 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1785)
      Titles at head: "Chester Higgins Jr Slide Sequences"; "Producer - Leslie Edwards"; "Black Women"; "Ten Seconds." Appears to be reused tape -- slide sequences are recorded for approximately first 11 minutes, followed by dance footage which is recorded over a public affairs interview with a Minneapolis alderman.
    - Ensemble Class, circa 1975-1980; cuid38071 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_273)
    - Black Music Ensemble Rehearsal, circa 1975-1980; cuid38078 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1786)
    - Ensemble III, March 19, 1976; cuid38086 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_863)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal, March 22, 1976; cuid38087 (Box 29, Audiocassette 481_829)
    - Composition Class, September 16, 1976; cuid38088 (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1896)
    - Composition -- Dixon, Benn, September 17, 1976; cuid38089 (Box 19, Audiocassette 481_062)
    - Teaching, Rehearsing, Etc., October 28, 1976; cuid38090 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_867)
    - Composition, November 5, 1976; cuid38091 (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1893)
    - Composition Class, November 12, 1976; cuid38092 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_769)
    - Composition Class, November 18, 1976; cuid38093 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_770)
    - Composition Class, November 19, 1976; cuid38094 (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1895)
    - Composition, 1976-1978; cuid38085 (Box 19, Audiocassette 481_061)
    - Composition D -- Advanced Composition for Dancers and Choreographers, circa 1977; cuid37976 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1843)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal, 1977; cuid38095 (Box 29, Audiocassette 481_830)
    - Class in Black Criticism -- Bill Dixon, Richard Tristman, L. Steiner, March 15, 1977; cuid38100 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1845, 481_1847, 481_1849)
    - Composition Class, April 7, 1977; cuid38101 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_780)
    - Ensemble Class, circa May 7, 1977; cuid37971 (Box 29, Audiocassette 481_781)
    - Ensemble Class, May 19, 1977; cuid38102 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_772, Box 29, Audiocassette 481_782)
    - Lecture and Demonstration on Composition, June, 1977; cuid38103 (Box 44, Audiocassette 481_2546)
    - "Theoretical Philosophical Implications of Improvisation as it Relates to 20th Century Composition and Performance" Lecture, June 9, 1977; cuid37101
      - Video -- 1 of 4, cuid41254 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1789)
        Format: EIAJ-1; Duration: 33 minutes; Preservation Note: Video quality is poor.
      - Video -- 2 of 4, cuid41255 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1783)
        Format: EIAJ-1; Duration: 33 minutes; Preservation Note: Video quality is unstable with heavy flagging.
      - Video -- 3 of 4, cuid41256 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1795)
      - Video -- 4 of 4, cuid41257 (Box 71, Half inch video reel 481_1794)
        The lecture ends 19 minutes in, and the remainder of the footage is travel and performance clips.
    - Composition D -- Advanced Choreography, Fall, 1977; cuid38098 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1841)
    - Composition D -- Advanced Choreography, Fall, 1977; cuid38099 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1844)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal, Fall, 1977; cuid38096 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_905)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Performance, Commons Theatre, September, 1977; cuid38104 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_761)
    - Improv Lecture, September, 1977; cuid38105 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 481_1279, 481_1280)
    - Intro to Ensemble Performance Commons Theatre, September 14, 1977; cuid38106 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_895)
    - Composition D -- Advanced Choreography, September 15, 1977; cuid38107 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1842, Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1874)
    - Advanced Composition for Dancers and Choreographers, September 22, 1977; cuid38109
      Includes excerpts of "Electronic Sonata" by Russell, "Daphnis and Chloe" by Ravel, and "Firebird" by Stravinsky
      - Audio (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1897)
      - Electronic Records
    - Intro to Ensemble, September 22, 1977; cuid38108 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_773, Box 31, Audiocassette 481_919)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Practices, Commons Theatre, September 23, 1977; cuid38110 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_774, 481_775)
    - Composition D -- Advanced Choreography, September 29, 1977; cuid38111 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1837)
    - Ensemble Class, September 30, 1977; cuid38113 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_778)
    - Introduction to the Art of Ensemble Performance, Commons Theatre, September 30, 1977; cuid38112 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_776, 481_777)
    - Black Music Lecture -- Nadi Quamar, October 4, 1977; cuid38114 (Box 76, U-matic 481_2365)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Practice and Performance, Commons Theatre, October 6, 1977; cuid38115 (Box 28, Audiocassette 481_779, Box 31, Audiocassette 481_912)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Performance, Commons Theatre, October 7, 1977; cuid38116 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_897, 481_900)
    - Lecture Demonstration on Theoretical and Philosophical Aspects, Commons Theatre, October 14, 1977; cuid38117 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_969, 481_907, 481_911, 481_968)
    - Ensemble Class, October 14, 1977; cuid38118
      - Video -- 1 of 3 (Box 73, U-matic 481_1761)
      - Video -- 2 of 3 (Box 73, U-matic 481_1763)
      - Video -- 3 of 3 (Box 73, U-matic 481_1757)
    - Advanced Composition for Dancers and Choreographers, October 20, 1977; cuid38120 (Box 40, Audiocassette 481_1873)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Performance, Commons Theatre, Ensemble Work-in-progress, October 20, 1977; cuid38119 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_899, 481_906)
    - Introduction to Ensemble Performance, Commons Theatre, October 21, 1977; cuid38121 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_913, 481_914)
    - Ensemble Class -- Devoted to Material for Leslie Winston's Senior Concert, November, 1977; cuid38122 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_901)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal and Lecture -- Material for Leslie Winston's Senior Concert, November, 1977; cuid38124 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_928)
    - Introduction to the Art of Ensemble Performance, November, 1977; cuid38123 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_910)
    - Introduction to the Art of Ensemble Performance, November, 1977; cuid38125 (Box 39, Audiocassette 481_1850)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal, December 16, 1977; cuid38126 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_909)
    - Orchestra Work -- Lecture and Demonstration, circa 1977-1978; cuid38097 (Box 44, Audiocassette 481_2544)
      This recording features Bill Dixon (Trumpet, Tenor Sax) and Stephen Horenstein
    - RESTRICTED: RESTRICTED Rehearsal in Commons Theatre, RESTRICTED Lesson with Parents Present, 1978; cuid38131 (Box 36, Audiocassette 481_1613)
    - Compilation Tape including Jennifer Keefe Class, circa 1978; cuid38028 (Box 38, Audiocassette 481_1806)
    - Ensemble Lecture and Rehearsal, 1978; cuid38127 (Box 22, Audiocassette 481_329)
    - George Barrow, circa 1978; cuid38026 (Box 23, Audiocassette 481_534, 481_535, Box 24, Audiocassette 481_544)
    - Composition D, Voice Studies with Jennifer Keefe, March, 1978; cuid38132 (Box 38, Audiocassette 481_1810)
    - Composition D, Visual and Performing Arts Building, March 16, 1978; cuid38133 (Box 20, Audiocassette 481_096)
    - Ensemble -- Class and Lecture, March 10, 1978; cuid38134 (Box 22, Audiocassette 481_336, 481_318)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal and Lecture on New Material, Commons Theatre, March 16, 1978; cuid38135 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_300, Box 31, Audiocassette 481_927)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal and Lecture on New Material, Commons Theatre, March 17, 1978; cuid38136 (Box 22, Audiocassette 481_310, 481_341)
    - Ensemble Class, March 23, 1978; cuid38137 (Box 22, Audiocassette 481_314)
    - Orchestra Piece for Jacobs -- Open Rehearsal, Commons Theatre, March 24, 1978; cuid38138 (Box 41, Audiocassette 481_1989)
      Duration: 89 minutes
    - Ensemble Class, March 28, 1978; cuid38139 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_301)
    - Ensemble Class, Commons Theatre, March 30, 1978; cuid38140 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_302, Box 22, Audiocassette 481_309, Box 29, Audiocassette 481_783)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal and Lecture, Commons Theatre, March 31, 1978; cuid38141 (Box 30, Audiocassette 481_890)
    - Ensemble Lecture, Commons Theatre, April 1, 1978; cuid38142 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_305, Box 22, Audiocassette 481_332)
    - Ensemble Class, April 6, 1978; cuid38144 (Box 31, Audiocassette 481_898)
    - Ensemble Rehearsal, Commons Theatre, April 6, 1978; cuid38143 (Box 22, Audiocassette 481_352)
    - Ensemble, April 13, 1978; cuid38145 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_299, Box 22, Audiocassette 481_354)
    - Ensemble Class, April 14, 1978; cuid38146 (Box 21, Audiocassette 481_291, Box 22, Audiocassette 481_328)